Guide to the Wells Rich Greene Inc. Records, 1954-1998 and undated RL.01365
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1954-1998 and undated (Acc. 98-0396), 140 boxes
  - Video and Film
    - [Procter & Gamble: Gain, see boxes 30-32, & 86] (Box 97)
    - Procter & Gamble: Gleem
      - 1. Gleem #1. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 97)
      - 2. Gleem #2--Friends. 1975. TRT: :30 (Box 97)
    - Procter & Gamble: OC-4
      - 1. OC-4--The Spa Family. 1984. TRT: 1:00 (Box 97)
      - 2. OC-4--The Spa Family Citrus Hill. 1984. TRT: 1:00 (Box 97)
      - 3. OC-4--Natasha / Revised. 1984. TRT: 1:00 (Box 97)
      - 4. OC-4--3 spots (all Concert). 1984. TRT: 3:00 (Box 97)
      - 5. OC-4--5 spots (all Concert). 1984. TRT: 5:00 (Box 97)
    - Procter & Gamble: Prell
      - R-1. Liquid Prell Master (Old Book) R-1. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 97)
      - R-2. Prell Master R-2. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 97)
      - 3. Prell Master 3. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 97)
      - R-4. Prell Master R-4. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 97)
      - 5. Prell Master Reel 5. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 97)
      - 28. Prell Historical TV Copy Review Reel spots (list enclosed; also Liquid Prell Copy Strategy Chronology--text). 1954-1977. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 97)
    - Procter & Gamble: Safeguard
      - 15. Safeguard Historical Reel--maybe 13 spots. 1977. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 97)
    - Procter & Gamble: Safeguard (continued) (Box 98)
      - Misc. 51. Safeguard--2 spots-- Confidence & Lessons. 1982. TRT: 2:00 (Box 98)
      - 54. Safeguard--Innocent Wife. 1982. TRT: :45 (Box 98)
      - 61. Safeguard--2 spots (both Give Your Body the Best). 1983. TRT: 1:15 (Box 98)
      - 77. Safeguard--Woman. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 98)
      - 90. Safeguard Soap--3 spots. 1987. TRT: 1:30 (Box 98)
      - 112. Safeguard--People Person Rev. (David Lucas & new VO). 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 98)
      - Safeguard--Happy Town--4 spots. Undated. TRT: Circa 2:00 (Box 98)
      - Safeguard-- Master Reel (Old Book 0 to 554). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 98)
      - Safeguard-- Master #1 (New Book). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 98)
      - R-2. Safeguard-- Master R-2. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 98)
      - 3. Safeguard-- Master R-3. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 98)
      - R-4. Safeguard-- Master R-4. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 98)
    - Procter & Gamble: Spic & Span
      - 1. Spic & Span Master Reel #1 (#1-37). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 98)
      - 2. Spic & Span Master Reel #3. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 98)
    - Procter & Gamble: Sure Deodorant
      - #1. Sure Master Reel 1--52 spots (listed on cover). Undated. TRT: Circa 40:00 (Box 98)
      - #2. Sure Master Reel 2 (old book). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 98)
    - Procter & Gamble: Sure Deodorant (continued) (Box 99)
      - R-3. Sure Master Reel 3. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 99)
      - R-4. Sure Master Reel 4. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 99)
      - R-5. Sure Master Reel 5. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 99)
      - R-6. Sure Master Reel 6. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 99)
      - 4. Sure Aerosol--American Song. 1976. TRT: 1:00 (Box 99)
      - Misc. 5. SURE--WORKING GIRL REV. 1977. TRT: 1:00 (Box 99)
      - 24. Sure--Sure Demos #1. 1977. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 99)
      - Misc. 33. Sure--2 spots--College Man & Housewife. 1979. TRT: 2:00 (Box 99)
      - 88. Sure Variety--Raise Your Hand Master. 1992. TRT: :45 (Box 99)
      - 139. Sure Deodorant--4 spots. 1988. TRT: 1:00 (Box 99)
      - 146. Sure--Raise Your Hand--89. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 99)
    - Procter & Gamble: V-30
      - 1. V-30--6 spots (all Black Magic). 1986. TRT: 3:00 (Box 99)
      - 2. V-30--2 spots--Black Is & Black is Family. Circa 1986. TRT: 1:30 (Box 99)
      - 3. V-30--Black Is Revised Master. Circa 1986. TRT: :45 (Box 99)
      - 4. V-30-- Black is Family Rev. Circa 1986. TRT: :45 (Box 99)
    - Procter & Gamble: Corporate
      - P& G 1. Corporate--2 spots (both Galaxy of Savings). 1977. TRT: 1:00 (Box 99)
    - Procter & Gamble: Corporate (continued) (Box 100)
      - P& G 2. Shower of Savings--5 spots. 1978. TRT: 2:30 (Box 100)
      - P& G 3. 14 Brands--Breakfast Couple. 1980. TRT: :30 (Box 100)
      - P& G 4. Olympic Promo--Turn Dimes Into Gold. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 100)
      - P& G 5. Citrus Hill Plus Calcium--3 spots (see boxes 95 & 97). 1986. TRT: 1:45 (Box 100)
      - P& G 6. Olympic Promotion--Winning Symbol. 1984. TRT: 15 (Box 100)
      - P& G 7. Procter & Gamble--2 spots (both Star Trek Video Game Offer). 1984. TRT: 1:00 (Box 100)
    - Ralston Purina: Test
      - Misc. 24. 1974. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 100)
    - Ralston Purina: Chex
      - R-1. Chex Master R-1 (new book). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 100)
      - 2. Chex Master #2. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 100)
      - 3. Chex Master #3. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 100)
      - A. Cereal Master Reel A (old book). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 100)
      - B. Chex Master Reel B. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 100)
      - 17. Bran Chex--Calif. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 100)
      - 17A. Bran Chex Historical Reel--20 spots (list enclosed). 1986. TRT: 1:00 (Box 100)
      - 18. Chex Cereals--2 spots. 1978. TRT: 1:00 (Box 100)
      - 28. Chex Cereals--Historical Reel. 1980. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 100)
    - Ralston Purina: Chex (continued) (Box 101)
      - 29. Chex--no list. 1980. TRT: 7:00 (Box 101)
      - 30. Ralston Purina Screening Reel. 1974. TRT: 15:00 (Box 101)
      - Misc. 34. Ralston Chex--2 spots. 1978. TRT: 1:00 (Box 101)
      - 97. Bran Chex Cereal--Eat and Go NFA Gag spot. 1986. TRT: :30 (Box 101)
      - 98. Bran Chex Brand Cereal--4 spots. 1987. TRT: 1:30 (Box 101)
    - Ralston Purina: Dog Chow
      - #1. Dog Chow Master Reel #1 (old book). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 101)
      - #2. Dog Chow Master Reel #2. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 101)
      - R-3. Dog Chow Master R-3. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 101)
      - R-4. Dog Chow Master R-4. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 101)
      - R-5. Dog Chow Master R-5. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 101)
      - R-6. Dog Chow Master R-6. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 101)
      - Misc. 14. Dog Chow--4 spots. 1977. TRT: Circa 2:00 (Box 101)
      - 18. Dog Chow-- (Compilation Reel) 78 spots (list enclosed). 1973-1976. TRT: Circa 39:00 (Box 101)
      - 18A. Dog Chow--Historical Reel--36 spots (list enclosed). 1972-1976. TRT: 18:00 (Box 101)
      - Misc. 22. Dog Chow--Liver Dog Chow (see also Box 124Misc 6 for 1 spot). 1977. TRT: :30 (Box 101)
    - Ralston Purina: French Toast
      - 1. French Toasties--5 spots. 1977. TRT: 2:30 (Box 101)
    - Ralston Purina: French Toast (continued) (Box 102)
      - 2. French Toast Cereal--4 spots. 1978. TRT: Circa 2:00 (Box 102)
      - 3. French Toastettes--2 spots. 1978. TRT: 1:00 (Box 102)
    - Ralston Purina: Freakies
      - 1. Freakies--Surf's Up. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 102)
      - 2. Freakies--Surf's Up (same as above--library copy). 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 102)
      - 3. Freakies--Cat's Bowl. Circa 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 102)
      - 4. Project Ha Ha / Freakies--2 spots. 1987. TRT: 1:00 (Box 102)
      - 5. Project Ha Ha--2 spots. 1988. TRT: 1:00 (Box 102)
      - 6. Project Ha Ha--Changes (animatic). 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 102)
    - Ralston Purina: GSGL (Grins & Smiles & Giggle & Laughs)
      - 1. 11 spots (list enclosed). 1977. TRT: 8:30 (Box 102)
    - Ralston Purina: Moonstones
      - 1. Moonstones--Kidnap. 1977. TRT: :30 (Box 102)
      - 2. Moonstones--Tank / Moonzoom. 1977. TRT: :30 (Box 102)
      - 3. Moonstones--Historical Reel--12 spots (list enclosed). 1977. TRT: 8:00 (Box 102)
      - 4. Moonstones--Kidnap / Limited Animation. 1977. TRT: :30 (Box 102)
    - Ralston Purina: Special Dinners
      - Composite Reel. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 102)
    - Ralston Purina: Tender Vittles
      - #1. Tender Vittles Master Reel (old book) (partial list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 102)
      - #2. Tender Vittles Master #2. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 102)
    - Ralston Purina: Tender Vittles (continue) (Box 103)
      - #3. Tender Vittles Historical Reel--26 spots (list enclosed). 1977. TRT: Circa 14:00 (Box 103)
      - R-4. Tender Vittles Master R-4 (partial list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 103)
      - 14A. Tender Vittles Historical#13-#25--18 spots (list enclosed.). Undated. TRT: 9:00 (Box 103)
      - 33. Tender Vittles--3 spots. 1981. TRT: 1:30 (Box 103)
      - 37. Tender Vittles--2 spots Pompadour & Gerald Rev #1. Circa 1982. TRT: 1:00 (Box 103)
      - 38. Tender Vittles--Confucious Picks. 1983. TRT: :30 (Box 103)
      - 40. Tender Vittles--The Clump. 1983. TRT: :30 (Box 103)
      - 41. Tender Vittles--The Clump. 1983. TRT: :15 (Box 103)
      - 42. Catviar--Tap Your Toes. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 103)
      - 43. Tender Vittles--2 spots Hockey Puck & Hercules. 1984. TRT: 1:00 (Box 103)
      - 44. Tender Vittles--Confucious Picks Rev. II. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 103)
      - 45. Tender Vittles--3 spots. 1984. TRT: 1:30 (Box 103)
      - 46. Goody Two Chews--4 spots. 1984. TRT: 1:30 (Box 103)
      - 47. Tender Vittles--The Clump Revised. 1984. TRT: :15 (Box 103)
      - 48. Goody Two Chews--6 spots. 1985. TRT: 3:00 (Box 103)
      - 49. Goody Two Chews--6 spots. 1985. TRT: 3:00 (Box 103)
    - Ralston Purina: Tender Vittles (continued) (Box 104)
      - 50. Goody Two Chews--6 spots. 1985. TRT: 3:00 (Box 104)
      - 51. Tender Vittles--Easy To Please. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 104)
      - 52. Tender Vittles--Chop. 1985. TRT: :15 (Box 104)
      - 53. Goody Two Chews--4 spots Master. 1985. TRT: 2:00 (Box 104)
      - 54. Catviar--2 spots (both Beyond Finicky) Master. Circa 1985. TRT: 1:00 (Box 104)
      - 55. Catviar--2 spots (both Beyond Finicky Rev.). 1985. TRT: 1:00 (Box 104)
      - 56. Catviar--Oceanliner Rev. 2. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 104)
      - 57. Catviar--Jonathan's World Master. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 104)
      - 58. Goody Two Chews--Revised Looking. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 104)
      - 59. Goody Two Chews--It Takes Two / Rev. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 104)
      - 60. Catviar--Oceanliner Rev. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 104)
      - 61. Catviar--Lord & Lady / Castle Rev. I. Circa 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 104)
      - 62. Catviar--Lord & Lady / Interview Rev. 1. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 104)
      - 63. Catviar--Orient Express Rev. I. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 104)
      - 64. Catviar--Beyond Finicky Canned Master. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 104)
      - 65. Tender Vittles--Cat Psychology. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 104)
    - Ralston Purina: Tender Vittles (continued) (Box 105)
      - 66. Goody Two Chews--Revised Looking / Talk. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 105)
      - 66 (again). Goody Two Chews--Revised Looking / Talk (copy of above) (Box 105)
      - 67. Tender Vittles--2 spots (both Cat Obedience). 1985. TRT: :45 (Box 105)
      - 68. Tender Vittles--Easy To Please / Historical w/o Art. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 105)
      - 69. Tender Vittles--2 spots (both Cat Groceries). Circa 1985. TRT: :45 (Box 105)
      - 70. Tender Vittles--3 spots. Circa 1985. TRT: 1:30 (Box 105)
      - 71. Tender Vittles--3 spots. Circa 1986. TRT: 1:30 (Box 105)
      - 71 (again). Tender Vittles--3 spots (same as above). Circa 1986. TRT: 1:30 (Box 105)
      - 72. Tender Vittles--Kangaroo. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 105)
      - 73. Tender Vittles--2 spots (both Lounge Act). 1987. TRT: 1:00 (Box 105)
      - 73A. Tender Vittles-- (same as above). 1987. TRT: 1:00 (Box 105)
      - 74. Tender Vittles--Lounge Act. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 105)
      - 75. Tender Vittles--2 spots (both Lounge Act) (Non-New). 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 105)
      - 76. Tender Vittles--2 spots (both Lounge Act Rev.). 1988. TRT: :15 (Box 105)
      - 77. Tender Vittles Lite--Lite Years (animatic). 1989. TRT: :15 (Box 105)
      - 78. Tender Vittles Lite--Lite Years Rev. (animatic). 1989. TRT: :15 (Box 105)
    - Reckitt & Coleman (Box 106)
      - 1. Airwick Botanicals--3 spots. 1992. TRT: 1:30 (Box 106)
      - 2. Airwick Project Tarzan--Where It Started. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 106)
      - 3. Carpet Fresh--Rolling Out / Rev. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 106)
      - 4. Carpet Fresh--Rolling Out. 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 106)
      - 5. Carpet Fresh--Rolling Out Final Video Storyboard. 1993. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 106)
      - 6. Airwick--2 spots. 1993. TRT: 1:45 (Box 106)
      - 7. Airwick Airwaves--2 spots. 1993. TRT: :45 (Box 106)
      - 8. Airwick Botanicals--4 spots. 1993. TRT: 2:00 (Box 106)
      - 9. Airwick Airwaves / Airwick Botanicals--2 spots. 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 106)
      - 10. Airwick Botanicals--Refreshing Rev (animatic). 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 106)
      - 11. Airwick Airwaves--Kitty Airwaves / Rev. 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 106)
      - 12. Airwick Airwaves--3 spots. 1993. TRT: 1:30 (Box 106)
      - 13. Stick Ups--2 spots (both Wide Open Spaces). 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 106)
      - 14. Stick Ups--2 spots (both Wide Open Spaces Rev.). 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 106)
      - 15. Botanicals--2 spots (both Refreshing). 1993. TRT: :45 (Box 106)
      - 16. Airwick Airwaves--2 spots. 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 106)
    - Reckitt & Coleman (continued) (Box 107)
      - 17. Airwick Airwaves--Flower. 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 107)
      - 18. Botanicals--Refreshing--Non New. 1993. TRT: :15 (Box 107)
      - 19. Botanicals--Refreshing--Non New. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 107)
    - Red Barn System
      - 1. Red Barn System--Previous Agency Comp Reel. 1976. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 107)
      - 2. Red Barn--2 spots (both Fresh Ideas-). 1977. TRT: 1:00 (Box 107)
      - 3. Red Barn--2 spots (see also Box 124--Misc 6 for 1 spot). 1977. TRT: 1:00 (Box 107)
    - Savin
      - Master Reel. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 107)
    - Seagram Beverage Company
      - 1. Wine Coolers--2 spots--Old Friends & Conversation. 1990. TRT: 1:00 (Box 107)
      - 2. Wine Coolers--2 spots. 1990. TRT: 1:00 (Box 107)
      - 3. Wine Coolers--2 spots (both Friend). 1990. TRT: :45 (Box 107)
      - 4. Wine Coolers--Conversation Alt II. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 107)
      - 5. Wine Coolers--Conversation. 1990. TRT: :15 (Box 107)
      - 6. TAOS Flipboards. 1990. TRT: Circa 4:00 (Box 107)
      - 7. Wine Coolers--3 spots. 1990. TRT: 1:15 (Box 107)
      - 7A. Seagram Equivalency--Conversation Rev. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 107)
      - 8. Wine Coolers--4 spots. Circa 1990. TRT: 1:45 (Box 107)
    - Seagram Beverage Company (continued) (Box 108)
      - 9. Seagram Coolers 1990 Sales Film. 1990. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 108)
      - 10. Seagrams Taos--Changes Master. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 108)
      - 11. Wine Coolers / Tropical Selection--2 spots (both Cooler). 1991. TRT: :45 (Box 108)
      - 12. Wine Coolers / Tropical Selection--Cooler / NBC Ver. 1991. TRT: :30 (Box 108)
      - 13. Wine Coolers / Tropical Selection--Cooler / Banc. Circa 1991. TRT: :30 (Box 108)
      - 14. Taos--2 spots (both Changes Rev.). 1991. TRT: 1:00 (Box 108)
      - 15. Wine Coolers--Cooler / :15. Circa 1991. TRT: :15 (Box 108)
      - 16. Taos--Splash w/end super. 1991. TRT: 32:15 ? (Box 108)
      - 17. Wine Coolers (Light) --Moments/Alt. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 108)
      - 18. Wine Coolers (light) --Moments/Alt.--NBC Ver. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 108)
      - 19. Wine Coolers--Olympic Vignettes (8 x :30). 1992. TRT: 4:00 (Box 108)
      - 20. Taos--3 spots (all Dance). 1991. TRT: 1:30 (Box 108)
      - 21. Taos Oasis--Oasis Master. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 108)
      - 22. Taos--5 spots. 1992. TRT: Circa 2:30 (Box 108)
      - 23. Taos Oasis--Oasis Rev. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 108)
      - 23A. Taos--Oasis (same as above). 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 108)
    - Seagram Beverage Company (continued) (Box 109)
      - 24. Cool Classic Coolers--3 spots (all Moments). 1992. TRT: 1:30 (Box 109)
      - 24A. Cool Classic Coolers--3 spots (same as above). 1992. TRT: 1:30 (Box 109)
      - 25. Wine Coolers--Changes Rev. 1992. TRT: 1:30 (Box 109)
      - 26. 2 Calorie Quest--2 spots (both Tongue Surfer). 1992. TRT: 1:30 (Box 109)
      - 27. 2 Calorie Quest--Tongue Surfer (director cut). Circa 1992. TRT: 1:00 (Box 109)
      - 28. Spritzer--Metamorph. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 109)
      - 29. Spritzer--Metamorph Rev. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 109)
      - 30. Seagrams Equivalency--Supersonic Sweepstakes Master. 1992. TRT: Circa :30 (Box 109)
      - 31. Seagrams Quest--2 spots Sleepwalker & Mirage. 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 109)
      - 31A. 2 Calorie Quest--Sleepwalker. 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 109)
      - 32. 2 Calorie Quest--3 spots. 1993. TRT: 1:30 (Box 109)
      - 33. Seagrams--Fantasy (rip-o-matic). 1993. TRT: 2:00 (Box 109)
      - 34. Quest--Real Life (rip-o-matic). Circa 1993. TRT: Circa :30 (Box 109)
      - 35. Quest--Extremely Alive (rip-o-matic). Circa 1993. TRT: Circa :30 (Box 109)
    - [Sheraton Corporation--ITT: see boxes 110-111] (Box 109)
    - [Sun Master: see box 112] (Box 109)
    - [Sunoco: see box 112] (Box 109)
    - Supercuts
      - 1. Supercuts--Exper / Rev. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 109)
      - 2. Supercuts--Fire Escape / Non-New / with Tag. 1984. TRT: :30 (Box 109)
      - 3. Supercuts--2 spots--Working Girls & Family. 1983. TRT: 1:00 (Box 109)
    - Sheraton Corporation--ITT (Box 110)
      - 1. Hammock Dunes. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 110)
      - 2. Palm Coast. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 110)
      - 3. Sheraton Hotels--4 spots. 1990. TRT: 1:15 (Box 110)
      - 4. Sheraton Hotels--5 spots. 1990. TRT: 1:30 (Box 110)
      - 5. Sheraton Hotels--Satisfaction / To Feel Happy. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 110)
      - 6. Sheraton Hotels--Hotels, Inns, Resorts, all-Suites. 1990. TRT: 1:30 (Box 110)
      - 7. Sheraton--5 Minute Sales Video Final for ITT Presentation. 1990. TRT: 5:00 (Box 110)
      - 8. Sheraton Historical Television Reel-- 36 spots (list on cover). 1970-Circa 1982. TRT: 23:30 (Box 110)
      - 9. Hotels--2 spots--Segmentation & Attitude. 1991. TRT: 1:00 (Box 110)
      - 10. Sheraton Hotels--2 spots--Segmentation Rev. & Attitude Rev. 1991. TRT: 1:00 (Box 110)
      - 11. Sheraton Hotels--The World. Circa 1991. TRT: :30 (Box 110)
      - 12. Sheraton Hotels Presentation Reel Master. 1991. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 110)
      - 13. Hotels--2 spots. 1992. TRT: 1:30 (Box 110)
      - 14. Hotels--Feel Like a Million. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 110)
      - 15. Hotels--Sure Savers. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 110)
      - 16. Sheraton--2 spots (both All Suites). 1992. TRT: 1:00 (Box 110)
    - Sheraton Corporation--ITT (continued) (Box 111)
      - 17. All Suites--All Suites. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 111)
      - 18. All Suites--All Suites / American In-flight. 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 111)
      - 19. Sheraton Hotels--2 spots. 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 111)
      - 20. Hotels--2 spots. 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 111)
      - 21. All Suites--2 spots (both All Suites Rev.). 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 111)
      - 22. Sheraton--2 spots (both Worldwide Expansion). 1993. TRT: 1:30 (Box 111)
      - 23. ITT/Sheraton--Our World Revolves Around You. 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 111)
      - 24. Sheraton--Our World Revolves Around You. 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 111)
      - 25. ITT/Sheraton--2 spots (both Our World Revolves Around You). 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 111)
      - 26. Corporate--5 spots (all Our World Revolves Around You) (World Cup Sponsor Vers.). 1993. TRT: 2:20 (Box 111)
      - 27. Sheraton Research Video. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 111)
      - 28. ITT Sheraton Hotels--O'Neill. 1995. TRT: :30 (Box 111)
      - 29. ITT Sheraton--2 spots (both Our World Revolves Around You Rev.). 1995. TRT: 1:30 (Box 111)
      - Sheraton Historical Reel. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 111)
    - Sloan Kettering
      - 1. Early Detection. Circa 1988. TRT: :15 (Box 111)
      - 2. Early Detection / Breast Cancer. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 111)
    - Sun Master (Box 112)
      - Compilation. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 112)
    - Sunoco (Sun Oil Company)
      - #1. Sunoco Master (old book) (Circa 38 spots--list enclosed). 1974-1978. TRT: Circa 17:00 (Box 112)
      - R-2. Sunoco Master R-2 (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 112)
      - #3. Sunoco Gasoline--Historical Reel--Circa 10 spots Master. Undated. TRT: Circa 5:00 (Box 112)
      - R-4. Sunoco Master R-4 (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 112)
      - R-5. Sunoco Canada Dry-5 (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 112)
      - R-6. Sunoco Canada Dry-6 (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 112)
      - R-7. Sunoco Canada Dry-7 (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 112)
      - Cam II 1. Cam-2--2 spots--Station & Store. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 112)
      - Misc. 40. Sunoco President. 1976. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 112)
    - TAG Heuer
      - 1. Tag Heuer--2 spots. Circa 1994. TRT: :55 (Box 112)
      - 2. Watches--19 spots (all Don't Crack Rev.). 1994. TRT: 9:30 (Box 112)
      - 3. Sport Watches--Don't Crack. 1995. TRT: :30 (Box 112)
      - 5. New Campaign--4 spots (all It's a Mind Game). 1995. TRT: 2:45 (Box 112)
      - 6. Master Edited Video w/ 2 spots. Circa 1995. TRT: 3:30 (Box 112)
      - 7. Sports watches--2 spots (both It's a Mind Game) Master. 1995. TRT: 1:45 (Box 112)
    - TAG Heuer (continued) (Box 113)
      - 8. Sports Watches--4 spots. 1995. TRT: 2:00 (Box 113)
      - 9. Sports Watches--37 spots (all Success It's a Mind Game / Different Personalities) (list enclosed) Master. 1995. TRT: 18:30 (Box 113)
      - 10. Sports Watches--13 spots (all Success It's a Mind Game / Different Personalities) (list enclosed). 1995. TRT: 6:30 (Box 113)
      - Tic Tac--Ferraro-- Master Reel. 1979. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 113)
    - Tooth Pro--Porat-Pro Inc.
      - 1. Tooth Pro--4 spots. 1978. TRT: 2:00 (Box 113)
      - 2. Tooth Pro--?. 1978. TRT: :20 (Box 113)
    - Tortel Beer
      - New Master--Steelers Wheel New Music Relay. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 113)
    - TWA
      - Misc. 3. TWA--Flip Wilson. 1977. TRT: 4:30 (Box 113)
      - Misc. 49. TWA--2 spots. 1981. TRT: 3:00 (Box 113)
      - 58. TWA--20 spots (list enclosed). 1976. TRT: 13:30 (Box 113)
      - R-1. TWA Reel I (old book 1 thru 23) Master. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 113)
      - R-2. TWA (old book 24-55) Master. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 113)
      - R-3. TWA R-3 (old book 59-72 & new book 1-35) Master. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 113)
      - R-4. TWA R-4 (new book 36-91) Master. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 113)
      - R-5. TWA R-4 (new book 93-99) Master. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 113)
    - United Industries
      - Master. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 113)
    - Union (Box 114)
      - Underoos Master Reel (20 spots--list enclosed). 1978-1983. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 114)
      - Underoos Master Reel (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 114)
    - US Magazine
      - 1. US Magazine--3 spots (all with Bee Gees). 1978. TRT: 1:30 (Box 114)
      - 2. US Magazine--3 spots (all with Linda Ronstadt). 1978. TRT: 1:30 (Box 114)
      - 3. US Magazine--Porter Bibb / US Logo. 1978. TRT: :30 (Box 114)
      - 4. US Magazine--3 spots (all with Travolta & Walters). 1978. TRT: 1:30 (Box 114)
      - 5. US Magazine--Roger Ebert / Generic / US Logo. 1978. TRT: :30 (Box 114)
    - Waring Products
      - 1. Ice Cream Parlor--John, John. 1977. TRT: :30 (Box 114)
      - 2. Ice Cream Parlor--John, John / X-mas. 1977. TRT: :30 (Box 114)
      - 3. Steam Chef--The Wearing Steam Chef. 1977. TRT: :30 (Box 114)
    - Warner
      - 1. Just Your Fit Bra Collection--Three Women. 1983. TRT: :30 (Box 114)
      - 1 (again). Warner Bra--Not a Stitch On. 1976. TRT: Circa :30 (Box 114)
      - 2. Just Your Fit Bra Collection--5 spots (all Three Women). 1983. TRT: 2:30 (Box 114)
      - 3. Perfect Measure--Perfect Measure in Store Video. 1987. TRT: :45 (Box 114)
    - J. Westino
      - Misc. 38. Magic Animals / State Fair / Polaroid / AT& T. 1980. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 114)
    - Westinghouse